An Inventory of the United States. Food Administration records XX066
Hoover Institution Archives
- Edwin Paul Shattuck, General Counsel of the United States Grain Corporation (USGC), London office files, 1911-1934, 1957. (Folder 270-300)
  - Norway, 1917-1918 (Folder 295: 20)
  - O correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 296: 1)
  - Organization (Food Administration), 1918 (Folder 296: 2)
  - P correspondence, 1918 (Folder 296: 3)
  - Railroads, 1918 (Folder 296: 4-8)
  - Requa, Mark L., 1917-1918 (Folder 296: 9-13)
  - S correspondence, 1917-1981 (Folder 296: 14)
  - U.S. Senate, 1917-1918 (Folder 296: 15-19)
  - Sheldon, L.P., 1917-1918 (Folder 297: 1-6)
  - Shipping Board, 1918-1927 (Folder 297: 7-10)
  - State Department, 1917-1918 (Folder 297)
  - Alphabetical file, 1918-1919 (Folder 297: 11-14)
    - Robert T. Lansing, 1917-1918 (Folder 297: 15)
    - Robert T. Lansing, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 298: 1-3)
    - Frank L. Polk, 1917-1918 (Folder 298: 4-5)
  - State food administrators, 1917-1918 (Folder 298: 6)
  - Sugar Division, George M. Rolph, 1917-1918 (Folder 298: 7-11)
  - T correspondence, 1917 (Folder 298: 12)
  - Tariff Commission, 1917-1918 (Folder 298: 13)
  - Tractors, 1917-1918 (Folder 298: 14)
  - Treasury Department, 1917-1919
    - Alphabetical file, 1917-1918 (Folder 299: 1-2)
    - G. R. Cooksey, 1917-1918 (Folder 299: 3)
    - William G. McAdoo, 1917-1919 (Folder 299: 4-5)
    - Arthur, Rathbone, 1918 (Folder 299: 6)
  - W correspondence, 1917-1918 (Folder 299: 7)
  - War Department, Alphabetical file, 1917-1918 (Folder 299: 8-10)
  - War Department, Newton D. Baker, 1917-1918 (Folder 299: 11-12)
  - War Department, Echoch H. Crowder, 1917-1918 (Folder 299: 13)
  - War Trade Board, W. K. Macy, 1917-1918 (Folder 299: 14-15)
  - War Trade Board, Vance C. McCormick, 1917-1919 (Folder 299: 16-17)
  - Wheat Export Company, 1917-1919 (Folder 300: 1-2)
  - Wheat guarantee, 1918 (Folder 300: 3)
  - Wilson & Co., 1917-1918 (Folder 300: 4)
  - Miscellany correspondence, 1920 (Folder 300: 5)
- Alphabetical file, 1906-1921. (Folder 300-314)
  See also boxes 88-203, 419-420
  - Bread and baking, 1917-1919 (Folder 300: 6-16)
  - Canada, Dominion Department of Agriculture, Livestock Branch, Market Intelligence Division, 1918-1919 (Folder 301: 1-6)
  - Central Bureau of Planning and Statistics, Statistical Clearing House, List of Labor Statistics, March 1919 (Folder 301: 7)
  - Cost of living, 1917-1919 (Folder 301: 8-9)
  - Dairy products, Butter, 1917-1918 (Folder 301: 10-13)
  - Dairy products, Cheese, 1917-1919 (Folder 302: 1-2)
  - Dairy products, Milk, 1917-1919 (Folder 302: 3)
  - Exports, 1916-1918 (Folder 302: 4)
  - Fats and oils, 1917-1919
    - General, 1918-1919 (Folder 302: 5-6)
    - France, 1918-1919 (Folder 302: 7)
    - Great Britain, 1917-1919 (Folder 302: 8-9)
    - Italy, 1917-1918 (Folder 302: 10)
    - Neutrals, 1917-1919 (Folder 302: 11)
    - Sweden, 1918-1919 (Folder 302: 12)
    - United States, 1917-1919 (Folder 302: 13-15)
    - United States, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 303: 1-4)
  - Food condition in Europe, 1917-1918 (Folder 303: 5)
  - Food situation, Foreign, 1915-1919 (Folder 303: 6-13)
  - France, Food Ministry, 1917-1918 (Folder 304: 1-6)
  - Grain, 1914-1920
    - The Cost of Wheat in the United States and in Europe, report by A.E. Taylor, 1919 (Folder 304: 7)
    - Stocks on hand, 1917-1918 (Folder 304: 8-11)
    - Barley, 1917-1919 (Folder 304: 12)
    - Corn, 1917-1918 (Folder 304: 13)
    - Oats, 1918 (Folder 304: 14)
    - Wheat, 1914-1920 (Folder 304)
      - Charts and maps, 1917-1918 (Folder 304: 15)
      - Elevator and warehouse reports, 1917-1920 (Folder 304: 16)
      - Elevator and warehouse reports, 1917-1920 (contd.) (Folder 305: 1-2)
      - Farms marketing, 1917-1918 (Folder 305: 3-4)
      - The World's Wheat, by James Wilson, 1919 (Folder 305: 5)
      - Acreage sown and abandoned average 1914-1917 (Folder 305: 6)
      - Buying Power of Wheat in War Time, report, 1918 (Folder 305: 7)
      - Flour, charts and maps, 1917-1918 (Folder 305: 8)
      - Reports on flours, meals, and cereals, 1918 (Folder 305: 9-11)
  - Great Britain, 1916-1919 (Folder 305)
    - Board of Agriculture and Fisheries, Return of Market Prices, reports, 1917-1919 (Folder 305: 12)
    - Food Ministry, 1917-1919 (Folder 305)
      - Bread, flour, and grain, 1917-1918 (Folder 305: 13-14)
      - Reports, weekly, 1917-1919 (Folder 305: 15-16)
      - Reports, weekly, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 306: 1-8)
      - Food Control Campaign, weekly bulletin, 1917 (Folder 306: 9)
      - Note on the Control of Food Distribution, by S. C. Tallents, 1918 (Folder 306: 10)
      - Weekly News Service, Propaganda Section, 1918-1919 (Folder 306: 11-13)
      - Notes on Rationing, by S. C. Tallents, 1918 (Folder 306: 14)
      - Economy News Service, Propaganda Section, circa 1918 (Folder 306: 15)
    - Food Ministry in U.S.A., Provision Section, weekly reports, 1918 (Folder 307: 1-3)
    - From the Food Production Department, weekly service reports, 1917 (Folder 307: 4-5)
    - Government Control of Trade, report, 1917 (Folder 307: 6)
    - Food (War) Committee, Royal Society, 1916-1917 (Folder 307: 7-12)
  - Imports of Food Stuffs to the United States, Statistical Division, reports, 1911-1919 (Folder 307: 13)
  - Legal Documents, Herbert Hoover's office, Books I-II, 1917-1919 (Folder 307: 14-15)
  - Legal Documents, Herbert Hoover's office, Books I-II, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 308: 1-8)
  - Livestock, 1910-1919 (Folder 308)
    - At Stock Yards, summary of reports, 1918 (Folder 308: 9-10)
    - Destinations of Livestock Loaded, reports, 1918-1919 (Folder 308: 11)
    - Receipts of calves at stock yards, 1917-1918 (Folder 308: 12-13)
    - Cattle and hogs, 1910-1919 (Folder 308: 14-15)
    - Meat Trade News, reports, 1918 (Folder 308: 14)
  - Markets, Statistical Review of the New York Market, 1911-1918 (Folder 308: 15)
  - Markets, Statistical Review of the New York Market, 1911-1918 (contd.) (Folder 309: 1-5)
  - Meat, 1916-1919 (Folder 309)
    - Meat and meat products summary, 1918 (Folder 309: 6)
    - Reports by Department of Agriculture, Bureau of Markets, 1918-1919 (Folder 309: 7-11)
    - Beef and beef products, 1916-1918 (Folder 309: 12-13)
    - Pork and pork products, 1916-1919 (Folder 309: 14-16)
  - Norway, Food Control Board, 1918-1919 (Folder 310: 1-4)
  - Prices, 1909-1919 (Folder 310)
    - Indices, 1911-1919 (Folder 310: 5-9)
    - Civil War and Great War, 1918-1919 (Folder 310: 10-11)
    - Dairy products, 1909-1917 (Folder 310: 12)
    - Grain, wheat and flour, 1917-1925 (Folder 311: 1-3)
    - Livestock, cattle and hogs, 1911-1918 (Folder 311: 4-5)
    - Relative, 1911-1918 (Folder 311: 6)
    - Sugar, 1971-1919 (Folder 311: 7)
    - Vegetables, 1906-1917 (Folder 311: 8)
  - Pork prices., See boxes 313-314
  - Programs, Imports, 1917-1919
    - General, 1917-1919 (Folder 311: 9-13)
    - Belgium, 1918 (Folder 311: 14)
    - Commission on Relief in Belgium, 1918 (Folder 311: 15)
    - France, 1918-1919 (Folder 312: 1-2)
    - Great Britain, 1917-1919 (Folder 312: 3)
    - Italy, 1918 (Folder 312: 4)
    - Grain, 1917-1919 (Folder 312: 5-10)
    - Meat and fats, 1918-1919 (Folder 312: 11-12)
    - Oils, 1918-1919 (Folder 312: 13)
    - Priorities, 1918 (Folder 312: 14)
    - Sugar, 1918 (Folder 312: 15)
  - Purchases, shipments, and arrivals, 1917-1919 (Folder 312)
    - Great Britain, 1918 (Folder 312: 16)
    - France, 1917-1918 (Folder 312: 17)
    - Italy, 1918 (Folder 312: 18)
  - Rations, 1917-1918 (Folder 312)
    - Food rations in the Belligerent Armies on the Western Front, 1918 (Folder 312: 19)
    - Foreign countries, 1917-1918 (Folder 312: 20)
    - Foreign countries, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 313: 1-4)
  - Switzerland, Federal Food Office, 1917-1918 (Folder 313: 5)
  - United States, Arable land, 1918 (Folder 313: 6)
  - United States Shipping Board, 1918-1919 (Folder 313)
    - World Shipping Data; Report on European Mission, by Edward N. Hurley, 1919 (Folder 313: 7)
    - "Report...Vessels Trading with the United States,", 1918-1919 (Folder 313: 8)
    - Allied Maritime Transport Council, reports, 1918 (Folder 313: 9-10)
    - Shipping Intelligence Section, reports, 1918-1919 (Folder 313: 11)
    - World Trade Board, Tabulation and Statistics Bureau, reports, 1917-1918. (Folder 313: 12)
      See also box 476-477
  - Pork prices, 1917-1921 (Folder 313)
    - Correspondence, reports, 1918-1919 (Folder 313: 13-17)
    - Correspondence, reports, 1918-1919 (contd.) (Folder 314: 1-6)
    - Food Administration Directory, 1918 (Folder 314: 7)
    - Congressional Record, Washington, Saturday, July 21, 1917 (Folder 314: 8)
    - Special licenses and regulations, 1919 (Folder 314: 9-11)
    - Miscellany, 1917-1921 (Folder 314: 12)
- Sidney A. Mitchell, attaché, American Embassy, London files, 1917-1918 (Folder 314-315)
  - Swiss Food Control, 1917-1918 (Folder 314: 13)
  - The Distribution of Sugar in France, 1918 (Folder 314: 14)
  - Note on the Control of Food Distribution (United Kingdom), by S. G., Tallents, 1918 (Folder 314: 15)
  - Notes on Rationing (United Kingdom), by S. G. Tallents, 1918 (Folder 315: 1)
  - A Perspective of the British Food Rationing System, by S. A. Mitchell and A. Smith, 1918 (Folder 315: 2)
  - The British Sugar Rationing Plan, 1918 (Folder 315: 3-4)
  - Food control forms and regulations in food rationing in the United Kingdom, 1918 (Folder 315: 5-8)
- May Bradford Shockley, Director of Food Conservation for Santa Clara County, California files, 1910-1922 (Folder 315-318)
  - Correspondence, alphabetical, 1917-1919 (Folder 315: 9-15)
  - "To the Local Food Chairmen," letters, 1918 (Folder 315: 16)
  - Letters of local chairmen arranged by districts, 1918-1919 (Folder 316: 1-10)
  - Alphabetical file, 1918 (Folder 316: 11-12)
  - Reports of local chairmen, 1918 (Folder 316: 13)
  - Thanksgiving dinners, 1917-1918 (Folder 316: 14)
  - Official Food Bulletin, San Francisco, California, 1918-1919 (Folder 316: 15)
  - Berkeley's War Work 1917; Mobilized Women's Organizations of Berkeley, February 20, 1918 (Folder 316: 16)
  - Report of the Number of Households in the Districts of Santa Clara County, 1918 (Folder 316: 17)
  - Belgian market lunch, 1918 (Folder 316: 18)
  - Food news for housekeepers, 1918 (Folder 316: 19)
  - The Community Kitchen, circa 1918 (Folder 317: 1)
  - National Dietary Survey, circa 1918 (Folder 317: 2)
  - Bulletins of food conservation, 1910-1919 (Folder 317: 3)
  - In Memorial G. Harold Powell, by Herbert Hoover, 1922 (Folder 317: 4)
  - Diplomatic List, Department of State, August, 1918 (Folder 317: 5)
  - The Stanford Bank Journal, August, 1918 (Folder 317: 6)
  - Official statements and addresses by Herbert Hoover, 1918 (Folder 317: 7)
  - Lists of sugar permits issued, 1918 (Folder 317: 8-13)
  - Official uniform for a woman, pattern, circa 1918 (Folder 317: 14)
  - University of California, Department of Home Economics bulletin, War Emergency Series, 1918 (Folder 317: 15)
  - "To the Women Directors," circular letters, 1918 (Folder 317: 16)
  - Meetings, 1918 (Folder 317: 17)
  - Official Food News, 1918 (Folder 318: 1)
  - Food conservation courses for colleges, 1918 (Folder 318: 2)
  - Formal (circular) letters, 1918 (Folder 318: 3-4)
  - Clippings, 1917-1918 (Folder 318: 5)
- Miscellany, circa 1918 (Folder 318-319: 6)
  - Miscellaneous files, 1917-1920 (Folder 318)
  - Cafeteria, 1917 (Folder 318: 7-8)
  - Public Information Department, 1917 (Folder 318: 9)
  - Grain Corporation, 1917-1919 (Folder 318: 10-13)
  - Trustee Fund, 1917-1920 (Folder 318: 14-17)
  - Trustee Fund, 1917-1920 (contd.) (Folder 319: 1-3)
- Library and Exhibits Section Records, 1909-1925 (Folder 319-368)
  - Brief outline of Washington organization, circa 1917 (Folder 319: 4)
  - Chronological Sketch with Directory of Members, May -June 1919, New York, March 1920 (Folder 319: 5)
  - Food Guide for the War Service at Home, with a preface by Herbert Hoover, 1918 (Folder 319: 6)
  - Food and the War; A Textbook for College Classes, 1918 (Folder 319: 7)
  - Food; News Notes for Public Libraries, volume one, Washington, D. C., 1917 (Folder 319: 8)
  - Food Problems, by A. N. Farmer and J. R. Huntington, 1918 (Folder 319: 9)
  - Reports, 1917-1918 (Folder 319: 10)
  - Exhibit of paintings, photographs, 1918 (Folder 319: 11)
  - Photographs and half tones of painting illustrating Herbert Hoover's speech Food Control-A War Measure, 1918. (Folder 320)
    See also box 465
  - Retail Stores Section, 1918 (Folder 321: 1)
  - Photographs of exhibit prepared by Harris Kennedy, 1918 (Folder 321: 2)
  - School exhibits, circa 1918 (Folder 321: 3)
  - Photographs from the Illustration Section, circa 1918 (Folder 321: 4)
  - Exhibits prepared by Exhibits Section, circa 1917 (Folder 321: 5)
  - Foreign posters photocopies, circa 1917 (Folder 321: 6-7)
  - Food Administration building photographs, Washington, circa 1918 (Folder 321: 8)
  - Charts, graphs, and maps, 1915-1918 (Folder 321: 9)
  - Charts, graphs, and maps, 1915-1918 (contd.) (Folder 322: 1-3)
  - Motor Transport Corps, photographs, 1918-1919 (Folder 322: 4-6)
  - Mats furnished to newspapers, circa 1918 (Folder 322: 7)
  - Food lines, photographs, circa 1918 (Folder 322: 8)
  - Food conservation exhibits, circa 1918 (Folder 322: 9-11)
  - Public library exhibit, 1918 (Folder 322: 12)
  - Community Food Demonstration materials, circa 1918 (Folder 322: 13-14)
  - Community Food Demonstration materials, circa 1918 (contd.) (Folder 323: 1-3)
  - Armstrong & Dunbar Schools exhibits, 1918 (Folder 323: 4)
  - Food conservation exhibits, circa 1918 (Folder 323: 5-11)
  - Food conservation methods taught in Community Food Demonstration, circa 1918 (Folder 323: 12)
  - Exhibits illustrations by subject, 1917-1918 (Folder 323)
    - Boy Scouts and Girl Scouts (Folder 323: 13)
    - Cheese (Folder 324: 1)
    - Corn (Folder 324: 2)
    - Destruction (Folder 324: 3-4)
    - Fats (Folder 324: 5-7)
    - Fish (Folder 324: 8)
    - Food saving (Folder 324: 9)
    - Food signs (Folder 324: 10)
    - Foods (Folder 324: 11)
    - Fuel (Folder 324: 12)
    - Lantern slides (Folder 324: 13)
    - Meat (Folder 324: 14)
    - Miscellany (Folder 325: 1-4)
    - Posters (Folder 325: 5-12)
    - Preserving (Folder 325: 13)
    - Sugar (Folder 325: 14-15)
    - Vegetables (Folder 326: 1)
    - Wheat (Folder 326: 2)
    - Women in industry (Folder 326: 3-9)
  - Photographs of exhibits by states, 1917-1918 (Folder 326)
    - California (Folder 326: 10-11)
    - Colorado (Folder 326: 12)
    - Connecticut (Folder 326: 13)
    - District of Columbia (Folder 326: 14)
    - Georgia (Folder 327: 1)
    - Hawaii (Folder 327: 2)
    - Illinois (Folder 327: 3)
    - Indiana (Folder 327: 4)
    - Iowa (Folder 327: 5)
    - Kentucky (Folder 327: 6)
    - Louisiana (Folder 327: 7)
    - Maine (Folder 327: 8)
    - Maryland (Folder 327: 9)
    - Massachusetts (Folder 327: 10-11)
    - Michigan (Folder 327: 12)
    - Minnesota (Folder 327: 13)
    - Missouri (Folder 327: 14-15)
    - Montana (Folder 327: 16)
    - Nebraska (Folder 328: 1)
    - New Jersey (Folder 328: 2)
    - New Mexico (Folder 328: 3)
    - New York (Folder 328: 4-5)
    - Nevada (Folder 328: 6)
    - North Carolina (Folder 328: 7)
    - Ohio (Folder 328: 8)
    - Oregon (Folder 328: 9)
    - Pennsylvania (Folder 328: 10-11)
    - South Dakota (Folder 328: 12)
    - Tennessee (Folder 328: 13)
    - Texas (Folder 328: 14)
    - Utah (Folder 328: 15)
    - Virginia (Folder 328: 16)
    - Washington (Folder 328: 17)
    - Wisconsin (Folder 329: 1)
    - Wyoming (Folder 329: 2)
  - Library exhibit handbook, by Milton Public Library, 1918 (Folder 329: 3)
  - Outlines and suggestions for exhibits and fairs, 1918 (Folder 329: 4-7)
  - Working Plans for Food Conservation Exhibit..., January 1918 (Folder 329: 8)
  - Suggestions for fairs and expositions in addition to Working Plans, 1918 (Folder 329: 9)
  - State Merchant Representatives for Michigan, exhibit suggestions, 1918 (Folder 329: 10)
  - St. Louis Patriotic Food Show, 1918 (Folder 329: 11)
  - Outline of Michigan Food Show, 1918 (Folder 329: 12)
  - Report of Committee on Statistics, presented at the Annual Meeting of the American Association of Fairs and Expositions, Chicago, 1917 (Folder 329: 13)
  - Effect of the Present War on the Fairs of 1918, by Oliver E. Remey, Secretary the Wisconsin State Fair (Folder 329: 14)
  - The Ministry of Food, summary of proposals, 1918 (Folder 329: 15)
  - Object Teaching by the United States Department of Agriculture, by F. Lamson Scribner, expert on exhibits, circa 1918 (Folder 329: 16)
  - Clippings regarding exhibits, 1918 (Folder 329: 17-20)
  - Clippings regarding exhibits, 1918 (contd.) (Folder 330: 1-3)
  - County fairs, plans and pictures, circa 1918 (Folder 330: 4)
  - Exhibit plans and suggestions, 1917 (Folder 330: 5)
  - Exhibits at state faire, 1918 (Folder 330: 6)
  - Conservation of Food Faire, Leominster, Massachusetts, 1918 (Folder 330: 7)
  - Handbook for Pennsylvania Train Exhibit, 1917 (Folder 330: 8)
  - Bulletin Board Use of Crop List, 1917 (Folder 330: 9)
  - Floor plan of Chicago Patriotic Food Show, 1918 (Folder 330: 10)
  - Exhibit suggestions, 1918 (Folder 330)
    - USFA Division (Folder 330: 11)
    - State press releases (Folder 330: 12)
    - Farm Journal press releases (Folder 330: 13)
    - Press releases (Folder 330: 14)
    - Statistical releases (Folder 330: 15)
    - Press releases for women's magazines (Folder 330: 16)
    - Newspaper published by the Washington Library director (Folder 330: 17)
    - Notes from libraries (Folder 330: 18)
    - College course outline (Folder 330: 19)
    - Books on food conservation (Folder 330: 20)
    - Working plans for exhibits (Folder 330: 21)
    - Outlines prepared by Dr. Hull on the food of Massachusetts (Folder 330: 22)
    - Recipe headings (Folder 330: 23)
  - Reports of Food Administration Library Publicity directors, 1917-1919 (Folder 331: 1-15)
  - Reports of Food Administration Library Publicity directors, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 332: 1-6)
  - Summary of reports, circa 1918 (Folder 332: 7)
  - Reports of exhibits and other activities arranged by the libraries of states, 1917-1919 (Folder 332: 8-13)
  - Reports of exhibits and other activities arranged by the libraries of states, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 333: 1-14)
  - Reports of exhibits and other activities arranged by the libraries of states, 1917-1919 (contd.) (Folder 334: 1-4)
  - Letters from librarians, 1917-1918 (Folder 334: 5)
  - Questionnaires on exhibits arranged by states, 1918-1919 (Folder 334: 6-16)
  - Questionnaires on exhibits arranged by states, 1918-1919 (contd.) (Folder 335: 1-16)
  - Conferences, American Library Association, 1918 (Folder 336: 1)
  - Chautauqua lecturers (Folder 336: 2)
  - Federal Food Administration (Folder 336: 3-7)
  - State Merchant Representatives of the USFA (Folder 336: 8-11)
  - Speeches, 1918 (Folder 336: 12)
  - Edith Guerrier, speeches, 1918 (Folder 336: 13)
  - Committee on Public Information, Division of Four Minute Men, bulletins, 1917-1918 (Folder 336: 14)
  - Correspondence arranged by states, 1917-1919. (Folder 337)
    Includes reports and printed matter
    - Alabama (Folder 337: 1-2)
    - Alaska (Folder 337: 3)
    - Arizona (Folder 337: 4)
    - Arkansas (Folder 337: 5)
    - California (Folder 337: 6-15)
    - California (contd.) (Folder 338: 1-2)
    - Colorado (Folder 338: 3-4)
    - Connecticut (Folder 338: 5-8)
    - Delaware (Folder 338: 9)
    - District Columbia (Folder 338: 10-12)
    - Florida (Folder 338: 13-14)
    - Georgia (Folder 338: 15-17)
    - Hawaii (Folder 339: 1)
    - Idaho (Folder 339: 2)
    - Illinois (Folder 339: 3-17)
    - Illinois (contd.) (Folder 340: 1-2)
    - Indiana (Folder 340: 3-8)
    - Iowa (Folder 340: 9-13)
    - Kansas (Folder 340: 14-15)
    - Kentucky (Folder 341: 1-3)
    - Louisiana (Folder 341: 4-5)
    - Maine (Folder 341: 6-7)
    - Maryland (Folder 341: 8-10)
    - Massachusetts (Folder 341: 11-15)
    - Massachusetts (contd.) (Folder 342: 1-10)
    - Michigan (Folder 342: 11-17)
    - Michigan (contd.) (Folder 343: 1-7)
    - Minnesota (Folder 343: 8-15)
    - Mississippi (Folder 343: 16)
    - Mississippi (contd.) (Folder 344: 1-2)
    - Missouri (Folder 344: 3-10)
    - Montana (Folder 344: 11)
    - Nebraska (Folder 344: 12)
    - Nevada (Folder 344: 13)
    - New Hampshire (Folder 344: 14)
    - New Jersey (Folder 344: 15)
    - New Mexico (Folder 345: 1-2)
    - New York (Folder 345: 3-14)
    - New York City (Folder 345: 15-16)
    - New York City (contd.) (Folder 346: 1-2)
    - North Carolina (Folder 346: 3-7)
    - North Dakota (Folder 346: 8-9)
    - Ohio (Folder 346: 10-15)
    - Oklahoma (Folder 346: 16-17)
    - Oregon (Folder 347: 1-4)
    - Pennsylvania (Folder 347: 5-13)
    - Porto Rico (Folder 347: 14)
    - Rhode Island (Folder 347: 15-19)
    - Rhode Island (Folder 348: 1)
    - South Carolina (Folder 348: 2-3)
    - South Dakota (Folder 348: 4-8)
    - Tennessee (Folder 348: 9-12)
    - Texas (Folder 348: 13-17)
    - Utah (Folder 348: 18-20)
    - Vermont (Folder 349: 1-2)
    - Virginia (Folder 349: 3-6)
    - Washington (Folder 349: 7-14)
    - West Virginia (Folder 349: 15-17)
    - Wisconsin (Folder 350: 1-7)
    - Wyoming (Folder 350: 8-13)
  - Press Releases, 1915-1918 (Folder 350)
    - Farm Journal, 1917-1918 (Folder 350: 14-18)
    - Farm Journal, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 351: 1-17)
    - Farm Press Periscope, 1918 (Folder 352: 1)
    - Press statements, USFA, 1917-1918 (Folder 352: 2-3)
    - States Section, Public Information Division, 1917-1918 (Folder 352: 4-12)
    - States Section, Public Information Division, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 353: 1-3)
    - States Section, Educational Division, 1918 (Folder 353: 4-10)
    - Miscellany, 1915-1918 (Folder 353: 11)
    - Magazine Section, 1917-1918 (Folder 353: 12-16)
    - Magazine Section, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 354: 1-15)
    - Magazine Section, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 355: 1-7)
    - Digest, 1917-1918 (Folder 355: 8)
    - Trade and Technical Section, 1917 (Folder 355: 9)
    - Religious, 1917 (Folder 355: 10)
    - The Social Hygiene Bulletin, New York, November 1918 (Folder 355: 11)
    - Boy Power, Washington D. C., July 15, 1918 (Folder 355: 12)
    - Weekly Bulletin, 1917-1918 (Folder 355)
    - Religious Press Section, 1917 (Folder 355: 13)
    - Trade and Technical Section, 1917-1918 (Folder 355: 14)
  - House of Representatives Acts 4961 and 4188, 1920 (Folder 355: 15)
  - Hearings before the Committee on Agriculture, House of Representatives, Washington, 1917 (Folder 356: 1)
  - Plans of Gordon Hotel, 1917 (Folder 356: 2)
  - Bulletin of the American Library Association, Chicago, September, 1918 (Folder 356: 3)
  - National Food Journal, issued by Ministry of Food, December 1917 and May 1918 (Folder 356: 4)
  - War Information Series, 1917-1918 (Folder 356: 5)
  - Statistical Department Information Service, 1917 (Folder 356: 6)
  - National School Service, by the Committee of Public Information, September-December 1918 (Folder 356: 7)
  - News Letter of the Women's Committee Council of National Defense, April-October 1918 (Folder 356: 8)
  - Women in the War; A Bibliography, by Marion R. Nims, 1918 (Folder 356: 9)
  - Herbert Hoover, biographical data, 1917-1918 (Folder 356: 10-13)
  - Check lists (index) of publications, 1917-1918 (Folder 357: 1)
  - Quota distribution for 107,996,000 publications, 1917-1918 (Folder 357: 2)
  - Food Administration publications, 1917-1918 (Folder 357: 3-14)
  - Food Administration publications, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 358: 1-15)
  - Food Administration publications, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 359: 1-13)
  - Food Administration publications, 1917-1918 (contd.) (Folder 360: 1-5)